SHELLA WARAMENA

+6285155412272 · shellawaramena@gmail.com · South Tangerang

SUMMARY

Project Manager with 5+ years experience in the Product Development sector. Prior exhilarate experience in Software Development, Digital Content Development and work with cross-functional team in fast-paced environment of project managing. Big passion to work in IT industry and committed to continually advancing my knowledge or relevant technologies.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Xcidic Pte Lte Dec 2024 - Present
IT Project Manager

- Ensuring the project development process carried out by the team accordance with business needs
- Translating business needs and stakeholder needs into product development needs
- Provide roadmap, timeline, and execution plan for the product features/functions
- · Prioritize and manage the backlog of new features and functions
- Resolving and/or escalating all blockers during the day to day operation
- Supports requests for proposals and presentations to support the growth of the project
- · Participate in daily scrum meetings, planning, reviews, and retrospectives

PT Centrinova Solusi Edukasi Project Manager

Dec 2021 - Dec 2024

- · Conducted day-to-day coordination across internal teams and vendors for project execution
- Created workload planner to manage resources load using Asana to meet timeline target
- Manage relationship with clients, vendors, and all stakeholders
- Worked collaborate with Instructional Designer, Graphic Designer, Animator and Developer and monitor the project progress
- Organized meetings with clients to discuss project goals and progress

PT Djelas Tandatangan Bersama IT Project Manager

May 2021 - Nov 2021

- Work collaboratively with Engineering, Marketing, Customer Support, UI/UX teams to implement new features and enhancements
- Provide reports, User Acceptance Test, and Project Documentation for Management Team.
- Monitor progress in design, development, testing of products, and documentation of work.
- Lead the Development Team in presenting progress reports and deliverables to Management Team
- Meet with clients to take detailed ordering briefs and clarify specific requirements of each project

PT Inspirasi Digital Eksperiensia Remote Project Manager

Jan 2021 - May 2021

- Specified requirements on a project to project basis and organizing them into chewable bites
- Managed time and resources to ensure that the team hits all deadlines.
- Served as main team and customer service interface to client groups
- Organized meetings with clients to discuss project goals and progress
- Conducted User Acceptance Test

PT Pratama Abadi Industri Project Manager

- Developed plans to keep Projects on budget and meet deadline
- Coordinated with cross functional team to achieve good quality physical product (sample shoe)
- Provide feedback to HQ, advise of any potential project issues, suggestion to assure project excellence & product consistency
- Communicated with Client across 5 geo on project progress
- Innovated sustainability for more environmentally friendly causing cost reducing up to -\$0.0061/pairs

EDUCATION

Universitas Pamulang

Magister of Computer Science

Universitas Pamulang

Bachelor of Computer Science (Honours) GPA 3.51 / 4.00

PROJECTS

Universitas Pamulang

- Centrinova | UOB HR System | March 2023 August 2023
 - Enhanced the existing HR system by adding a Condolence System feature, improving employee support during critical moments.
 - Finish the project within 3 months.
 - Successfully integrated the feature, streamlining the process and reducing manual workload for HR staff.

Centrinova | Alef Education | September 2022 - March 2023

- Alef Education is a global education technology company based in the capital of the United Arab Emirates, Abu Dhabi.
- Help Client to develop Math digital content, simulation game, and machine learning for Islamic Junior High School for 7,8,9 grade
- Successfully finished the project within 9 months

• Harnods | BTP Ranger & Villager | January 2021 - May 2021

- BTP Ranger is an Android & iOS application for teachers to be able to report on each student's progress, daily activities, chat with parents.
- BTP Villager is an Android& iOS application for parents, where parents can find out updates on their child's development, their activities at school, chat with their teachers.
- BTP is a Singaporean pre school.
- Successfully launched the app with major features: two-way chat, student weight & height report, photo album, weekly plan.

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Software Development
- Budgeting and Cost Analysis
- Problem Solving
- Negotiation

- Communication Skills
- English
- Collaborative